

# Natália Mitsuko

UX / UI Designer

Maceió, AL - Brasil

### About me

With 4 years of experience as a Brazilian UX/UI Designer and a background in Psychology, I integrate design with an understanding of the user, strategically mapping their needs. I stand out in the field of interface design for my continuous search for harmony between aesthetics and usability.

atymitsuko@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/natymitsuko/

Be behance.net/natymitsuko

#### Languages

Portuguese (BR)

English (USA)

## Work Experience

EDGE Innovation Center (UFAL)

UI/UX Designer (2022 - Now)

Centro de Pesquisa Easy (UFAL)

UI/UX Designer (2022 - 2023)

Sua Formatura (Startup)

UI/UX Designer (2021 - 2023)

# **Education background**

MBA UX Design and User Research

Leandro Rezende / Unifast (2024)

UX Unicorn Program (Course)

Leandro Rezende (2023)

UI Design with visual references

Udemy (2021)

Figma: Collaborative Design

Udemy (2021)

Psychology Graduation

UNIT - AL (2016-2020)

## Hard skills

Figma	
Figjam	
Illustration	
Miro	